<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidStudio2DGame</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Logo">Image</string>
    <string name="Email">email</string>
    <string name="Forgot_password">forgot password?</string>
    <string name="Sign_up">sign up</string>
    <string name="Log_in">log in</string>
    <string name="Password">password</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="tutorial_base_building_text">"Base Building Tutorial
Introduction - Welcome to the Base Building Tutorial! In this guide, you will learn the fundamental steps to construct and manage your base efficiently.
1. Starting Your Base
1a. Choose a Suitable Location - Ensure the area is resource-rich and defensible.
1b. Lay the Foundation - Build a Command Center or Headquarters as the core structure.
1c. Resource Gathering - Place resource collection buildings like mines, farms, or extractors.

2. Expanding the Base
2a. Add walls, towers, and traps to protect your base.
2b. Storage Facilities - Construct storage units for collected resources.
2c. Production Buildings - Build factories or workshops for unit creation and upgrades.

3. Monitor Efficiency - Optimize building placement to reduce travel time.

4. Defense and Security
4a. Fortify Weak Points  - Identify vulnerable areas and reinforce them.
4b. Strategic Placement** - Position turrets and towers near entry points.

5. Advanced Tips
5a. Expand Gradually - Avoid over-expansion to prevent resource strain.
5b. Scout Surroundings - Explore nearby areas for threats and opportunities.
6. Conclusion Congratulations! You now have the knowledge to build and maintain a strong base. Keep refining your strategies and adapting to new challenges as they arise. Good luck!  "</string>
</resources>